ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/166 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 6, 1946-1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 5: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1950 to May 31, 1951. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Central Dramatic Group of the ILGWU Presents Its Drama Festival, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. June 9, 1951. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Communist Party: Enemy of Negro Equality, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Herbert Hill. Reprinted from The Crisis, June-July, 1951. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Dear Colleague, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. September 6, 1951; October 22, 1951. Correspondence.From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: 16mm Sound Films Available to ILGWU Locals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Mark Starr. September, 1951. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Historia de la ILGWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Max D. Danish; Bernard Seaman; A. Reina. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 11: Report on the Officers' Qualification Courses, 1937-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Mark Starr. June, 1952. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Statement on Education Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    By Education Department. November 19, 1952. Includes November 20, 1952 cover letter by Mark Starr. From Publications. vol. 6. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 7, 1947-1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Dear Fellow Egg-Head Operator in Workers' Education., Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Mark Starr. December 30, 1953. Correspondence. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The ILGWU Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt, and Reefer Makers' Union of Greater New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: ILGWU Officers' Qualification Courses. Test no.1, Economics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: ILGWU Officers' Qualification Courses. Test no.2, Economics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 5: Union Members Learn to Live and Lead, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. Reprinted from the 20th Anniversary Yearbook of Adult Education. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Newsletter no.3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. March, 1954. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Educational Program: Spring 1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. Broadside. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Dear Colleague, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Mark Starr. January 7, 1953. Correspondence. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Instruction Sheet for Semi-Annual Report Educational Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 10: Educational Program: Winter-Spring 1953, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 11: Elementary English Reader: Lessons 1-5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Simon Beagle. January, 1953. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Elementary English Reader: Lessons 6-10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Simon Beagle. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Elementary English Reader: Lessons 11-15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 14: Elementary English Reader: Lessons 16-21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 15: Report of the Education Department., Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    By Education Department. June, 1951 - May, 1953. From Publications. vol. 7. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Publications. vol. 8, 1946-1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Dear Colleague, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. April 14, 1954. Correspondence. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Yak-Yak., Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. Newsletters 5-7. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Committeeman: A Skit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Suzanne Roberts; Jane Scheuer. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Educational Department, ILGWU, Reports 34th Year., Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Mark Starr. Press release. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Educational Program: Fall, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. Broadside. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Educational Work of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Here's Our Hand, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. Flyer. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: How Lucky Is My Social Security Number?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 9: Learning, Playing, Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Fannia Cohn. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Movies with Discussions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 11: Problems? We All Have Them. You Can Get Help., Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 12: Radio Stations Run by Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Frederick F. Umhey. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Registration: A Skit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 14: Save Life and Liberty with the ILGWU Women's Health Brigade., Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 15: Stick to Your Union Bunch, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 16: Tomorrow's World, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 17: UNESCO: Its Objectives and How To Implement Them, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Fannia Cohn. From Publications. vol. 8. Third copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: With These Hands, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By Education Department. Film advertisement. From Publications. vol. 8. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Quarter Century Mark, 1917-1942, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Reprinted from Justice, June 15, 1942. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Quarter Century Mark, 1917-1942, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Education Department. Reprinted from Justice, June 15, 1942. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1937-1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  3 copies
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1937 - May 31, 1938. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1939-1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1939 - May 31, 1940. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1940-1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1940 - May 31, 1941. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1941-1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1941 - May 31, 1942. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1944-1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1944 - December 31, 1946. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1946-1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Education Department. June 1, 1946 - May 31, 1948.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1953-1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report of the Education Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Education Department. June, 1953 - May, 1956. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Report of the Educational Department., 1966; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of the Educational Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Social Psychology for the Worker., 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  A Syllabus for Discussion Groups by Becky Chalmers Barton. December 1940.
  - Item 1: Social Psychology for the Worker., Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Becky Chalmers Barton. Syllabus for Discussion Groups, School For Workers, University of Wisconsin, December 1940. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Songs., 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Songs., Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Statement on Education Policy, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Statement on Education Policy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Education Department. November 19, 1952. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Stick to Your Union Bunch, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Stick to Your Union Bunch, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Education Department. Broadside. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. The Story of the I.L.G.W.U., 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Story of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., 1934-1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  English and Spanish. 1934; 1947; 1950; 1955; 1959 (2 copies).
  - Item 1: Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Estructura y Funcionamiento de la I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By A. Reina. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Structure and Functioning of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Suggestions for Social, Educational, and Recreational Program for Our Local Unions., 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  August 1934.
  - Item 1: Suggestions for Social, Educational, and Recreational Program for Our Local Unions., Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Education Department. August 1934.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Las Trabajadores de la Aguja Tambien Tienen su Union., 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Spanish. Reprint from Eces de Nueva York, no.409 (1954:Sep. 5).
  - Item 1: Las Trabajadores de la Aguja Tambien Tienen su Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Education Department. Reprint from Eces de Nueva York, no.409 (1954:Sep. 5). Item is in Spanish.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Garment Jobs., 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  October 1940.
  - Item 1: Training for Garment Jobs., Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Leon Stein. October 1940. Second copy. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service. How the New York Dress Board Works., 1940-1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: How the New York Dress Board Works., Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    By Phillip Kapp. Training for Trade Union Service.. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service. Publications. [vol. 1] [folder 1 of 2], 1938-1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Plan for ILGWU Officers' Educational Qualifications, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Education Department. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Adventures in Industrial Citizenship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By William Hard. October 15, 1940. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: First Aid for Organizers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Function of the N.Y. Dress Joint Board Complaint Department., Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Murray Gross. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The ABC of Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Israel Horowitz. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Government Publications of Interest to Workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Joel Seidman. March, 1940. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: How the Death Benefit Fund Works, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Hyman A. Schoolman. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: How the New York Dress Board Works., Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Phillip Kapp. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Human Responsibilities of Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Meyer Perlstein. July 4, 1943. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Industrial Control in the Coat and Suit Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By F. Nathan Wolf. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Keeping the Financial Records of the ILGWU, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Siemon L. Hamburger. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor-Capital Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Meyer Perlstein. July 13, 1940. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Merle D. Vincent. October 19, 1937. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Neckwear Industry and Its Organization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Joseph Tuvim. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Negotiation and Enforcement Problems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By David Dubinsky. March 2, 1936. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: New Members' Class, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Doris Preisler. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The New York Dress Industry Placement Unit, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Helen Whipple. December 3, 1940. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Organization Problems in the Southwest, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Meyer Perlstein. July, 1939. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Organizing the Handkerchief Industry in Passaic, N.J., Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Anna Kula. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Organizing in Montreal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Bernard Shane. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Problems Involved in the Newark Strike, 1935, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Sadie Roisch. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Problems of a Local Manager, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Jacob Heller. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Questions and Answers About Local 66 ILGWU, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Zachary L. Freedman. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Question of Week-Work or Piece-Work in the Cloak Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    By Isidore Nagler. April, 1933. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service. Publications. [vol. 1] [folder 2 of 2], 1938-1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: In Defense of "Contractor Limitation" and "Jobbers' Responsibility" Clauses, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Isidore Nagler. April, 1935. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Co-Operation with South America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Alfonso Henriques dos Santos Correa. March 3, 1942. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Educational Department Launches Civilian Defense Program for New York Locals, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Education Department. Defense Series 4. January, 1942. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Educational Qualification Courses for Officers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Essential Qualities for Union Leadership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: The Role of Local 102 (Drivers and Helpers) in the Cloak Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Saul Metz. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Rules for a Shop Chairman, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Aaron Schwartz. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Running of Conventions and Meetings, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Rebecca Jarvis. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Settling Prices in Dresses., Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Ann Gould. January 31, 1938. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Strategy of General Strikes in the Cloak Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Isidore Nagler. March 9, 1936. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Strikes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By H. Greenberg. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Strike Publicity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Frank Palmor. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Strike Relief Methods and Policies of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Helen G. Norton. March, 1940. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Strike Gains, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 15: Structure and Function of the New York Cloakmakers' Joint Board, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Isidore Nagler. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Structure and Problems: Eastern Division Cotton Dress and Miscellaneous Dress Department, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Elias Reisberg. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Suggestions for Educational Activities in Connection with National Defense Service., Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Education Department. Defense Series 3. December, 1941. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Underwear Division of the Women's Garment Industry and the Agreement, 1937, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Samuel Shore. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Unemployment in Cloak Division: Its Cause and Cure, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Simon Farbber. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 21: Union Finance at a Glance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Education Department. February, 1939. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Voluntary Label and The Union Label, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Charles Green. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: What Makes a Good Union Organizer, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Harry Wander. October 21, 1938. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: When and When Not to Strike, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 25: The Work of the Business Agent with Sample Day and Problems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    By Arthur S. Samuels. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. [vol. 1]. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Educational Department. Training for Trade Union Service. Publications. vol. 2, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Background and Special Features of Trade Union Accounting., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Siemon L. Hamburger. From the Accounting Forum, December, 1946. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Day in the Life of a Business Agent with Sample Problems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Arthur S. Samuels. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Garment Workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Education Department. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: How To Build Your Union., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: The I.L.G.W.U. Quiz, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Abe S. Weiss. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Leadership Training Institute, Roosevelt College, Chicago, ILL., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Tamaara Danish. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Organizing the Garment Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Education Department. May-June, 1937. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Overlapping in the Needle Trades, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By George Wishnak. December, 1938. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Trade Union Techinques. Test no.4., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Who Sets the Styles?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Training for Union Service, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Mark Starr. Training for Trade Union Service. From Publications. vol. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Womens Garment Industry., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)